HERE Organizing Department Las Vegas Strike Files 6199/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Organizing Department Las Vegas Strike Files
1984-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/003
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
5840644
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 25, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6199 AV: HERE Audio-Visual Materials 6199 G: HERE Graphics 6199 MB: HERE Memorabilia 6199 mf: HERE Records on Microfilm 6199 PUBS: HERE Publications 6199/001: HERE Legislative Department Files 6199/002: HERE Western Region Local Files 6199/003 mf: HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/004: HERE Locals files 6199/004 mf: HERE Locals Files on Microfilm 6199/005: HERE Communications Department Files 6199/005 P: HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/006: HERE General Executive Board Files 6199/006 mf: HERE General Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/007 mf: HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm 6199/008 mf: HERE General President's Files on Microfilm 6199/009 mf: HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm 6199/010 mf: HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm 6199/011 mf: HERE Official Journals on Microfilm 6199/012 mf: HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/013: HERE Historical Files 6199/013 P: HERE Historical Photographs 6199/014: HERE Conventions Files 6199/015: HERE Editor Files
Hotel & Restaurant Employees International Union
5840644
- Las Vegas Project Organizing Campaigns (1 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Las Vegas Project Organizing Campaigns (2 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Downtown Four, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Holiday Inn, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Las Vegas Organizing Project (1 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Las Vegas Organizing Project (2 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Las Vegas Organizing Project (3 of 3), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Scope and Contents
  Newspaper Articles, Clippings, etc.
- Las Vegas Project Expenses, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Binion's Horseshoe Strike, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Las Vegas Strike, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Articles and Clippings
- Las Vegas Hate Letters, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Las Vegas Strike Video, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Las Vegas Strike Correspondence and Replies (1 of 2), 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Las Vegas Strike Correspondence and Replies (2 of 2), 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Las Vegas Strike, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Mailings, Letters, Flyers, etc.
- Las Vegas Strike Expenses, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)